MOHPREET KAUR

mohpreet.kaur8@gmail.com ◆ Cell +1 249-288-7290 ◆ https://mohpreetk.github.io/

CAREER SUMMARY

Experience 4 months Co-op as a Data and Analytics Technician

2+ years in Direct Sales.

Languages Swift, C#, HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript (ES 2020, ES2021), SQL, DAX

Tools XCode, Visual Studio, Visual Studio Code, SSMS, PowerBI, Microsoft Suite

Frameworks Entity, React, Bootstrap

<u>Portfolio</u> Used JavaScript, CSS3, HTML5 (Animations, Media Queries, Responsive design)

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Easy Financial

Mississauga, ON

Sales Admin - Pilot

08/2022 - Present

Increased the Web Application Conversion rate by approx. 2% within 5 months.

Financial Services Representative

03/2022 - 07/2022

- Improved the Personal Sales numbers by 200+% in the first 3 months of starting.
- One of the Top performers in the Sales of Ancillary Products.

Regional Municipality of York

Newmarket, ON

Data and Analytics Technician

09/2021 - 12/2021

Technologies: PowerBI, DAX, M

 Successfully reworked and launched the Region's Hospital Performance Dashboard providing the user 70% more information expanding from 4 Sheets to 9 interlinked sheets.

Georgian CollegeBarrie , ON

Peer Mentor 01/2021 - 12/2021

 Helped over 60 mentees settle into the college life by organizing group meetings and providing one on one support, becoming an excellent resource for all queries.

PROJECTS

Memory Master [Code]

05/2021 - 08/2021

Technologies: XCode, Swift, MacInCloud, Storyboard, Interface Builder

- Individually worked on a tile match game applying the fundamentals of Swift, MVC, and OOP.
- Documented requirements, process flows, and presentations for the user.
- Used Core Data to store user stats.
- Built assets for different themes and backgrounds.

Decor and Handicraft Merchant [Code] [Link]

01/2021 - 04/2021

Technologies: ASP.NET C#, Azure, Entity, Razor Pages, HTML/CSS/JS, MSSQL, SSMS

- Reproduced a shopping cart website to list and sell products.
- Used ASP Identity and Authorization for User Authentication and Login IDs.
- Added payment gateway through Stripe.
- Google SSL Login.

EDUCATION

Undergraduate Diploma in Computer Programming

Barrie, ON

Georgian College

01/2021 - 12/2021

- Secured overall GPA of 96.37/100 with Dean's List
- International Student Leadership Award & Board of Governor's Medal Award

JavaScript Courses (Modern JS Features) - Self-Learning

Remote - 2021